(Leonard:)-I am. I'm really proud.
-Yeah.
(Amy(on webcam):)Hello, Sheldon.
Is everything okay?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Why?
(Amy:)Well, the last time you made
an unscheduled video chat,
(Amy:)there was a curly fry
in your regular fries
(Amy:)and you thought someone might be
trying to slip you a mickey.
(Sheldon:)April 13...
(Sheldon:)A dark night, indeed.
(Amy:)So what can I do for you?
(Sheldon:)I'm calling to invite you
(Sheldon:)to a spontaneous date night
tomorrow evening.
(Penny:)-Really?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)You were kind enough to watch
Raiders of the Lost Ark with me.
(Sheldon:)So I'd like to return the favour
by inviting you to watch an episode
(Sheldon:)of your favourite childhood
television series,
(Sheldon:)Little House on the Prairie.
(Amy:)That sounds lovely.
(Amy:)Why are you rubbing your hands
together?
(CLEARS THROAT)
(Sheldon:)I'm putting on lotion.
Are you in or not?
(Amy:)Of course I'm in.
(Sheldon:)Excellent.
Then I shall see you tomorrow.